ADRIANA GUERRA

adriana.luz.guerra@gmail.com 📞 +1 949 763 8167 (in) linkedin.com/in/a-l-guerra





SKILLS

- JavaScript
- VΒ
- C#
- ASP.NET
- .NET Framework
- .NET CORE
- HTML
- CSS
- SQL
- VBA
- MS Access

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA. BERKELEY

Graduated May 2007 **BA** in Cognitive Science

SOFT SKILLS

- Leadership
- Teaching/Mentoring
- Troubleshooting
- Communication

LANGUAGES

- English: Native
- Spanish: Fluent
- French: Proficient

ADDITIONAL

US Citizen

PROFILE

I am a self-motivated developer dedicated to the pursuit of well-designed software and systems. Working in a variety of fields, from SCUBA diving to neuroscience research, has given me the opportunity to develop strong skills in the interpretation of user needs and to apply my development skills to wide a variety of projects. I am interested in developing efficient systems that are user-friendly and versatile.

EXPERIENCE

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Self Employed, 2017 - Present

Developed business management software for SCUBA diving centers using MS Access, VBA, SQL, ASP.NET, C#, VB.NET, and Javascript . I streamlined the customer registration process through a registration form accessible by media device and simplified business activities such as course registrations, product purchases, and employee pay sheets by consolidating them into one user-friendly data management system. I am currently working on converting our student management tools into a web app for SCUBA instructors and dive centers.

PROGRAM COORDINATOR

Roctopus Pro Center, Koh Tao, Thailand, 2018

Reorganized and oversaw a SCUBA diving professional training program. During my time with Roctopus Pro, I developed a training schedule to maximize opportunities for trainees while minimizing redundant work for the limited staff. I also developed Google Sheet and Google Script based program management tools to track training progress easily, revamped the out-dated website, developed HTML email templates, oversaw social media, and responded to program inquiries.

INSTRUCTOR

Sairee Cottage Diving, Koh Tao, Thailand, 2013 - 2018

Worked as a head SCUBA diving instructor at a well regarded dive shop in one of the busiest diving locations in the world. As a head instructor I was responsible for teaching courses of all levels, from introductory experiences to courses for aspiring professionals. My responsibilities included organizing diving trips and mentoring interns while ensuring the safety of all of my divers.

STAFF RESEARCH ASSOCIATE

Univeristy of California, San Diego, 2010 - 2012

Worked with the Research on Aging and Development Lab and the Swartz Center for Computational Neuroscience. My responsibilities included collecting neurobehavioral measures (i.e. electroencephalography, eye tracking, body motion capture, and behavioral tests) from typical and clinical populations, analyzing data using specialized software, and developing protocols and Python scripts to test the accuracy of data stream integration from various data sources with varying sampling rates.

Additional experience available upon request.